var data = [
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 130+125+191?",
    "answers": ["335", "456", "446", " 426"],
    "correct": "446"
  },
  {
    "question": "If we minus 712 from 1500, how much do we get?",
    "answers": ["788", "778", "768", " 758"],
    "correct": "788"
  },
  {
    "question": "50 times of 8 is equal to:",
    "answers": ["80", "400", "800", " 4000"],
    "correct": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "110 divided by 10 is:",
    "answers": ["11", "10", "5", " None of these"],
    "correct": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "20+(90÷2) is equal to:",
    "answers": ["50", "55", "65", " 60"],
    "correct": "65"
  },
  {
    "question": "The product of 82 and 5 is:",
    "answers": ["400", "410", "420", " None of these"],
    "correct": "410"
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the missing terms in multiple of 3: 3, 6, 9, __, 15",
    "answers": ["10", "11", "12", " 13"],
    "correct": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Solve 24÷8+2.",
    "answers": ["5", "6", "8", " 12"],
    "correct": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Solve: 300 – (150×2)",
    "answers": ["150", "100", "50", " 0"],
    "correct": " 0"
  },
  {
    "question": "The product of 121 x 0 x 200 x 25 is",
    "answers": ["1500", "0", "4000", " None of these"],
    "correct": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the next prime number after 5?",
    "answers": ["6", "7", "9", " 11"],
    "correct": "7"
  }
];
